You
All right
Used to comment the channel news has learned that two construction workers
have been killed while others may still be buried alive
I
Buddy just come down
My construction company has built a dozen easy to build is we've
never had anything more than a minor injury
What are you implying don't look at me?
Sequencing issues and construct well, maybe you missed something you took the
proper safety precautions. How would something? Oh, no
I am NOT gonna take the fall on this
Who the hell are you?
Dr. Lightman, thank you so much for coming down right away Steven.
Right. Dr. Lightman is here to assist FEMA in the rescue effort
Assist how he's a deception expert. He's worked with FEMA on half
a dozen cases. I want you to give me a full cooperation
Who's Lord? Well, you're all pointing fingers and shifting blame which is
typically the disaster rescue operation
I'm just gonna guarantee you one find you man
We pulled out nine men two in body bags three are still
missing one Denman and kiss her
How long have been gone 15 hours?
No sign of him find any sign of him standing around here
talking either
We Kevin Warren I own Green City construction those are my men
buried down there
They're my men to those missing men are all from Frostburg Meredith
Fallon. I'm the mayor
This is the city engineer Mark Woolwear. Thank you, dude. We've been
focusing our search here
Southeast Quadrant 2b
That's what the missing men were last seen collapse brought down six
stories of concrete right on top of them our experience if we
don't get
To them within 24 hours the odds of finding them alive go
way down
You better move fast, don't you you want to talk to first
I need to talk to whoever saw him last
I've got an early meeting tomorrow that I need you and local
to take on your own. Did you find dr.
Leibman FEMA confirmed he's at the disaster site. I'm heading out there
now while there's still one or two people
He hasn't had time to alienate better drive fast
Oh
That foster foster yes, dr. Leibman is waiting for you come this
way
Yeah, we were all in the same sub crew
We're working together since we built these foundations and you left the
men just before the collapse
Yeah, like two three minutes at the most we were laying down
a rebar Southeast Quadrant and I had to take a leak
So I was in and out of the John and then I
felt the ground shaken and I hit the dirt
I
Thought you know, he's got a trap down there and I can't
even get to him. I can't imagine. Hey must be filling right
now
I don't think you have any trouble imagining how you're feeling right
now. What I think you imagine this whole story of time
Call me a liar. Oh your eyes calling you a liar
We just work it when people feel genuine guilt. They always look
down and away. You were looking straight at us
The search team hasn't been able to find the men where you
said they were
We're just trying to understand what happened here
It says here that you were hurt on a construction job earlier
this year had you at a commission for almost three months
Yeah, I almost broke my neck on a non-union contract. I was
lifting pylons
I
Expression DC expression. What emotion do you think this person is feeling
right now?
No angry no surprise
Embarrassed happiness
This one
Disgusted correct
Having trouble recognizing every emotion except disgust. It's a pattern we found
sometimes with people who are addicted to opiates
You can recognize disgust because you see it over and over from
your friends and family
I'm guessing that after you ran out of pain meds for your
neck injury. You started self-medicating. Hey, I've done tons of drugs
Understand completely mr. Spaley. Did you lie about where you were before
the collapse because you were getting high someplace else?
Hey
He's a gesture and who's that and who's that? I know their
names. They're missing mr. Spaley
Okay, look I came up I went to my locker and I
got my stash all right
I was lost track of time, but I wasn't going down there
more than an hour
You saw the men in the southeast quadrant an hour before the
collapse
This entire operation has been focused on to be in the essence
To be in the SC part based on what you told us
it could be anywhere on any level
Oh
Let's hope the dogs are lying, too
I
Thank you for meeting with me.
What can we do for you today, Mr. Kashani?
I've read about your marriage experiments, and I had my people do
a little research into
The work you do here.
Okay.
Long and short is, I'm about to ask my girlfriend, Nadia, to
marry me.
Oh, Mazel Tov.
It's a good thing you're starting young.
It took my dad five times to get it right.
Fair, alcohol, green card problems, affair.
So, when my mom and I were together, I was in a
relationship.
And I was like, I'm not going to marry you.
I'm going to marry you.
Oh, Mazel Tov.
It's a good thing you're starting young.
It took my dad five times to get it right.
Fair, alcohol, green card problems, affair.
So, when my company, NetWorker, went public, I did, well...
Yeah, I helped banking $4.5 billion doing very well.
Before I propose to Nadia, I have to know she loves me
for the right reasons.
What makes you think she doesn't?
Nadia grew up with nothing.
Her father was a short-order cook in and out of work.
She struggled with money her whole life.
Student loans, credit card debt.
So?
So.
Right after my company went public, my partner's wife left him and
took their two-year-old
Daughter.
She used the little girl against him for a huge settlement.
So what is it you'd like us to do?
Nadia says she had no idea who I was before we met.
I just want to make sure she's telling the truth.
Dr. Lightman does deception detection for the FBI, TSA, police.
We don't snoop into people's personal lives.
But thanks for coming in.
Your website's incredibly useful for reconnecting with girls who rejected me in
middle school.
Look, just do your boss a favor and make a decision after
you look.
I think that's the micro-expression for holy crap.
We're dropping fiber optic cameras into the collapsed structure, and the crawler
drills
Will be boring through the debris to create a hole through which
we will then pull out
The metal.
Mayor Fallon?
And we have every reason to believe that Mr. Blunt, Mr. Denman,
and Mr. Kisker are
Alive.
And the drills are the best way to reach the men?
They've been down there for 19 hours now.
We need to reach them as quickly as possible.
No expense will be spared to save them.
And I want to reiterate that no wrongdoing has occurred in the
construction on this site.
You know, I'm going to let you handle the questions.
I really have to get back to the families.
Excuse me, I'm going to get back to the families.
Mayor Fallon.
Hi, I'm Jillian Foster.
I know who you are.
We really appreciate your help here.
Hi.
Any idea how this happened?
No.
You lied when you said there was no wrongdoing on the site.
Why was that?
That was just a...
Oh, it's just what?
I pressured the Green City Construction to hire more Frostberg workers than
they needed.
None of our men would have even been there if it weren't
for me.
How did you pressure them?
Permits and zoning.
I helped them clear some bureaucratic hurdles.
I don't know what things are like for you DC folks,
But things have gotten real bad for Frostberg with the recession.
The site was going to bring a whole new industry here.
Our Silicon Valley, thousands of new jobs.
If I can help with anything else, please call my office.
Thank you.
We've got video!
There they are!
They're alive!
Can I see that?
No.
Kevin, thank you.
It's Vaughn, Kevin, and Kisker!
It's Kisker.
His leg's crushed.
There's a lot of blood.
I can't really feel my thumb.
Oh my god, baby.
Someone's gotta help him.
We are trying, Mrs. Kisker.
We rigged the tourniquet on it.
But he's not doing so good.
Jared, are you hurt?
I'm okay, Valerie.
We're all banged up, but we're okay.
I love you, Valerie.
All right, let's get you back to the staging area.
I will keep you updated.
I'm staying here.
I'm sorry, we have to bring you back to the tent.
Dr. Lightman.
My men need engineers and rescue workers,
Not a couple of freak show shrinks pointing fingers.
She's the shrink.
I'm the freak show.
I'm sorry, we normally wear labels.
Hello?
Hello, yeah, we're here.
Can you tell me what happened?
The sub-roofs just started coming down.
Well, sweetheart, we went to the elevator shaft,
But we couldn't get there in time.
Is there any way you can get over there now?
We tried, but the substructure floor
Between here and the shaft is just too unstable
To give out.
We're gonna have to get out of here.
The substructure floor between here and the shaft
Is just too unstable to give out.
He's right, we haven't even completed
That substructure floor yet.
We're gonna make a bleed out down there.
We have to drill faster.
Listen, guys, I promise you,
We're gonna get you guys up from out of there, okay?
You just sit tight.
The drill should reach in a couple of hours,
And we're gonna do whatever it takes.
You're gonna be rescued.
You see that?
Yeah.
See what?
Hey, um, Mr. Blunt?
Yeah.
Mr. Blunt, can you hear me?
We lost the feed.
Can you trace the line?
Guys, talk to me.
I need to know why we got cut off.
We got men down there.
We need to communicate with them.
All right, give us a minute.
We're working on it.
Can you rewind it back to the point
Where they'd just been told they were gonna be rescued?
These two men are showing joy and relief.
Hey.
Wait, can you freeze it there?
Hey, can we push in on this now?
Okay.
Lips stretched.
Can you pan up to the ice?
Ah, it's retracted.
Fear.
That's concealed fear.
While he's buried under 50 tons of concrete and steel,
What kind of would you expect?
Relief?
I don't expect a man who's just been told
He's gonna be rescued to show fear.
And everyone else is showing relief.
Maybe he doesn't believe he can be rescued.
Post-traumatic stress can stifle almost any positive emotion.
Maybe, uh, Mr. Glump doesn't want to be rescued.
Who wouldn't want to be rescued?
Someone who caused the collapse in the first place.
You think Glump might have intentionally caused the collapse?
Well, that would explain the look of fear.
Best explanation we've got.
This is unbelievable.
How long has Jared Glump worked for you, Mr. Warren?
About six months.
Any problems?
Any threatened violence against the company?
Yeah, he confronted me a few times.
In fact, he sent a threatening letter to my office
Complaining about overtime.
Why aren't you firing?
Well, believe me, I tried.
The union blocked me.
Why would Glump sabotage the building while he was still inside?
Well, maybe he got trapped down there.
We replayed the video game.
Okay.
We're up.
We're all banged up, but I think we're okay.
I love you, Valor.
Wait, freeze it! Freeze it!
Look at that.
It's charring on the concrete.
Burn marks from an explosion.
Damn.
What's wrong?
Blunt could have used explosives to try to blow up the building.
That could have caused the collapse.
If he did this, he could be trying to sabotage our rescue
efforts, too.
There could be more explosives down there.
What about my other guys?
We need to get them out of there.
They're trapped right here in the northwest quadrant.
If they could get across to the elevator shaft here,
They'd be protected from another explosion.
No way. This floor is too unstable to get there.
They'd never make it.
We're getting ready to send rescue workers down there.
If there are undetonated explosives, I can't move forward.
Dr. Leibniz, can you find out from Blunt if he did this,
So we know if it's safe to get these men down there?
To get the live feed back up, I could sort him directly.
Well, we have to get it back up, then.
We won't get anything from Blunt that way.
He's not going to admit to blowing up the building
If he's still down there with his crew.
Well, then what the hell are we going to do?
Because we're just wasting time here,
And Kiskers down there bleeding.
The violence in the workplace correlates to domestic violence.
Guy doesn't blow up a building
Without that anger spilling over at home.
We should talk to his wife.
My father would have been proud of these men.
He was mayor. It was his dream to try to bring industry
to our city,
And we're fulfilling that dream.
And I am proud of our strength in this difficult time.
And once we get the men out...
Excuse me. Is Valerie Blunt here?
...we'll rely on each other to get through this...
Thank you.
...just as we always have.
I know you're concerned, and I'll take questions one at a time.
Please.
We met in high school.
I was the cheerleader, and Jared was third string running back.
Ridiculous, right? But we fell in love.
Are you still in love?
Of course. I mean, you know, it's...
It's not perfect. It's...
It's a marriage.
I can't believe this happened after everything else this year.
You and your husband have been through a lot?
Uh, no. No, no, I just mean, um...
With how hard it is to find work around here for anyone.
Maybe it's just crazy.
What?
Your husband, maybe he's just bonkers.
What? What are you...
He was arguing with the company. He was constantly getting into fights,
right?
What my partner is dancing around here is that we think
Your husband just lost it and blew up the building.
Jared would never do that. What are you doing?
This isn't appropriate.
There's something she's not telling us. We're wasting time.
I'm sorry.
I'm sick of watching you cuddle these women.
I'm sick of you derailing this investigation.
You little bitch.
Who the hell are you people?
Stay away from me.
You almost didn't sell it. I'm gonna have to hit you harder
next time.
You know, you take a little bit too much pleasure in that
one.
Valerie Blunt was disgusted when you slammed her.
But she wasn't afraid.
She showed no heightened sensitivity to violence between a man and a
woman.
I think it's unlikely she was abused.
So you don't think your husband could have blown up the building?
With no violence at home, it's hard to believe.
It's, uh, it's Loker. Give me a second.
Yeah.
Take it.
Oh, is that a joke?
Yeah.
You want to tell me what it is?
I don't need your permission to take on a case.
Well, it depends on the case, doesn't it, really?
It'll be fine. I promise.
That usually means I'm getting screwed.
Usually.
Isn't that the head of Green City Construction?
Warren with Mrs. Blunt?
Less than a foot and a half between them.
Flash glass from her.
For a quick turn away.
They've been intimate before.
You know, Valerie Blunt,
Was hiding something when you asked if she and her husband had
problems.
Island's flooded.
That's something she didn't want to say.
Maybe her husband wasn't the perpetrator.
Maybe he was the target.
So Warren sleeps with Blunt's wife
And then buries him alive.
If you think I would have anything to do with this,
You are completely out of your mind.
Why would I sabotage my own job, my own company?
For a woman?
And I got ten guys on this crew, at least,
Who can tell you exactly where I've been on this site
Every minute of the last three days.
I've been down on the substructure for weeks.
But you and Mrs. Blunt had an affair, right?
It wasn't an affair.
They were separated at the time.
And he'd hardly spoken to her for six months before they broke
up.
Why did your relationship end?
I just wasn't into it anymore.
You know, I told her I just wasn't really feeling it, you
know?
That's a lot of anger, Josh, huh?
For a woman you don't care about,
Men usually reserve that kind of anger for women that they love.
I don't know why it ended, okay?
I thought we were on cloud nine.
We both felt like we were kids again.
We were at the dinner one night, she got a phone call
from Blunt.
She spoke to him for about five minutes,
And she pulled it out of the restaurant.
I don't know if she went running back to him just like
that, so...
You believe him?
Well, he's pretty confident about his alibi.
Yeah, and he used similes and metaphors
When he was talking about Valerie Blunt.
We were on cloud nine, we felt like kids again.
People don't use that kind of language when they're lying.
What do you think Blunt told her that brought her running back
to him?
There's something going on between them.
You still don't know why he showed fear when he found out
he was going to be rescued.
What else did Loca found on the footage?
It's hot down here, but they're still there.
Can you zoom in on his left cheek and forehead, Sylvia?
Oh, there's that thing again.
What is that, contempt?
It could be contempt. It's unilateral.
Hey, I need to borrow Michael.
We're going to go meet our billionaire's girlfriend, Nadia Dawson.
Wow.
Easy, tiger. She's only into guys making ten figures.
Maybe she really loves him.
Yeah. Right.
What makes you so sure?
The female hanging fly.
What?
She'll only mate with the male when he brings her a caterpillar
as a food offering.
The bigger the offering, the more time she will have intercourse with
him.
For insects it's food, for us it's money.
She's a female hanging fly.
Okay, you need to get out more.
Look, I don't care if she's into him for his money, as
long as she is upfront about it from the beginning.
Yeah, well, it's not always so easy to be open about money.
I always tell women exactly how much I have in the bank
on the first date.
And you wonder why you never get a second.
Drip lap. Dr. Lightman's on the line.
Hey, so it's a contraction of Blunt's orbicularis, corrugator, and frontalis muscles?
I'm thinking contempt. Maybe he did try to bring the building down
after all.
No, that's not contempt.
Well, what is it?
Mr. Blunt's a very sick man.
I wouldn't feel too well either if I were buried under a
building.
I know he was sick long before he was buried.
I almost got the feedback up.
How's your husband?
How'd you know? Don't do that.
Can you still hear us?
Yeah.
We hear him now.
Got it. How's Mr. Kisker?
He's not good. You need to get us out of here.
Mr. Blunt, I need you to tell us something.
What is it?
On the video footage we got of you back here, I noticed
something a little peculiar.
You have a rippling contraction of your facial muscles.
I don't understand.
Well, you haven't been well, have you?
What do you mean?
Your muscle contraction is a symptom of late-stage multiple sclerosis.
No. No.
I don't know what you're talking about.
When you and your wife were separated,
Something that you told her over the phone brought her running back
to you.
Are you sick?
Mr. Blunt, it's okay.
Mr. Blunt, your friend could bleed to death.
I never meant for any of this to happen.
We got no savings. I don't have insurance.
The doctor said I got a few years.
I didn't want to leave out with nothing.
When you were told you were going to be rescued, you looked
scared.
What were you afraid we were going to find out?
I was working near an elevator shaft.
My hands were shaking a lot.
I was trying to hold on to my blue torch, and I
couldn't, and it fell.
From B1 to floors down to B3.
The tank must have exploded.
I didn't realize what was between you guys in danger. I swear.
Hello. Can I help you?
Are you Nadia Dawson?
Yes.
Hi.
I'm Christina.
I'm Christina Lopez. I was three years behind you in North Columbus.
You created softball for Miss Sleavy. Pitcher, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. She always said you had the best pick-off move.
That is so funny. Are you staying here at the hotel?
I'm sorry, what was it, Christina?
Yeah, I was just here for a meeting. You've been working here
a long time?
Almost a year.
Turns out Georgetown actually wants you to pay for classes.
How weird, running into someone from NC High.
Right here.
Miss Sleavy would always say,
You got four bases, three strikes, two teams, but only one winner.
So what brought you to DC?
Well, my boyfriend started a company that's based here.
It's one of those social internet sites the kids are into.
Oh, which one?
It's called NetWorker.
You're dating the founder of NetWorker?
Wow, how'd that happen?
What do you mean?
I mean, it's just a long way from North Columbus.
Yeah, I guess so.
But how'd you meet him?
Yeah, it's the funniest thing. I'd obviously heard of the company, but
I had no idea who he was.
I just saw this adorable guy standing right here at the bar
trying to get a drink.
Yeah, that is funny.
It must be strange to come from North Columbus and not be
with someone so well off.
Take a look at this, Mr. Kishani.
You got four bases, three strikes, two teams, but only one winner.
That's Nadia telling the truth.
She's talking with her hands. It's what we call illustrators.
But when she's asked if she knew who you were when you
met...
Yeah, it's the funniest thing. I'd obviously heard of the company, but
I had no idea who he was.
I just saw this adorable guy standing there at the bar.
No more illustrators. Her hands are in her lap.
It must be strange coming from North Columbus and now to be
dating someone so well off.
Instead, she touches her watch and her earring.
Manipulators. When you see illustrators decrease and manipulators increase, scratching, licking the
lips, or in this case, touching jewelry, it's a sign of lying.
I can't believe this.
Whatever she told you, she knew who you were when you met.
You have my check. Mr. Kishani, I don't want to see anymore.
Mr. Kishani, I thought he was coming back in tomorrow.
He said he couldn't wait.
What did you tell him?
The truth. She's after his money.
That's not the whole truth.
It's all he wanted to know.
Yeah, but that's not all we found out.
We're sure it was an accident.
Of course it was. We knew that our men would never intentionally
do harm to the building.
Mayor Fallon is right. We ruled out the possibility of explosives. Should
be able to reach the men within the hour.
What was the exact cause?
Detonation of a blowtorch, a settling tank, dropped through the substructure by
Mr. Blunt.
That man doesn't believe a word he just said.
No, he doesn't.
The specifics of the collapse pattern are consistent with Blunt's description.
Maybe he knows what really happened.
Hey, Stevens. You got a problem?
The city engineer doesn't believe a blowtorch caused the building to collapse.
Of course he does. He said so.
No, the engineer is lying. He knows something about how this collapse
happened.
Come on. Five minutes ago you guys told me Blunt caused a
collapse. Who the hell am I supposed to believe?
Well, I'll tell you not to believe.
That guy.
I've been in love with the same woman for 31 years.
The same woman for 32 years.
Thanks for coming back in, Mr. Cushemi.
I don't understand why I'm here.
Well, the fact that Nadia knew who you were before you met
isn't the only thing we learned when I talked to her.
Okay.
Look at this.
And the way he hates breakfast food and how frustrated he gets
in traffic.
I don't know. I just love everything about him. I want to
spend the rest of my life with him.
There. That's an illustrator.
There, she is telling the truth.
She does love you. And your money.
You're lying to yourself if you think you can separate the two.
She lied to me.
Well, why are you in love with Nadia?
She's charming, she's intelligent, and oh, wait for it. She's beautiful.
How's her beauty any different from your money?
I don't know.
Exactly.
Just be honest with her.
And yourself.
And get a prenup.
I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't shrug my shoulder.
You don't believe the blowtorch caused the explosion, do you, Mr. Bullwair?
Yes, I do.
What's he doing?
11 beats every five seconds. That's 132 beats per minute.
What are you talking about?
Your carotid artery is pulsing 132 beats per minute.
Your heart's racing. Why is the tent?
Maybe you found something in your inspections that could have caused the
collapse.
I didn't find anything.
Now that's the truth. Now you're lying to yourself.
Now that's the truth. Now you're telling the truth.
So I'm thinking maybe you didn't find anything in your inspections because
you didn't do the proper inspections.
There are three men trapped underneath us.
And if you know there's a problem and something happens to them,
it's going to be your fault.
My wife and I were three payments behind on our mortgage. We
were going to get foreclosed.
I don't know where the hell the money came from.
Money?
And a note.
From who?
I don't know. It just said to skip the inspections and sign
off on the approvals.
Well, why would someone pay you up? What was it they didn't
want you to find?
Look, usually these inspections are pro forma. I'm sure someone just wanted
to move things along fast.
Mr. Bullwair, you don't believe that's all it is.
You're playing down your responsibility for what's gone wrong.
You don't want to admit how big a risk you really took
with these men's lives.
But you need to tell us, what is the worst thing somebody
could be trying to hide on this site?
There. There.
What do you think?
As soon as the drill is over, we'll be able to get
the money.
I'm sure you'll be able to get the money.
As soon as the drills allow us to pull them through, we're
going to get your husband out of there.
Please. He's everything. Just get him out of there.
Hey, Stevens.
You have to.
You will. This is one. I promise.
Yes, sir. I'm training.
What are you talking about?
Training.
We can't drill. There could be methane gas down there.
Methane?
If there's methane down there, Blunt's blowtorch could have ignited it, causing
the explosions.
The drills could sell off another one.
Environmental testing was done on this site months ago. There's no signs
of any gas.
I took a bribe. Proper inspections weren't done.
What?
I went back over the old geologic surveys. Decades ago, this entire
area was a landfill.
And there could be methane seeping up from it.
How could you have signed off without the inspections?
Just stop the drills and do the testing.
Methane testing takes hours. These men have been trapped for almost a
full day.
One man is dying down there. We could lose him while we
do this testing.
Hey, someone paid this man not to do his job. You don't
care who or why?
I'll let the cops deal with him. I'm not wasting any more
time.
I am saving this man. We are drilling.
Eight to one.
What?
Eight to one. Average ratio of firefighter deaths in the U.S. compared
to every other country with the same training, effectiveness and equipment.
So what?
We have a hero complex in this country. Our firefighters rush in
too quickly trying to live up to the expectation that they're heroes
and more of our men get killed.
Step back. And that is in order. Now!
All move! Ten more feet! Power up to 800 RPM!
You guys all right?
It's hard to breathe. The air is getting thick.
Is that the methane?
It could explode. The drills could set it off.
You gotta tell them what's going on.
This is the city engineer. I think there's a pool of methane
seeping up from underneath you.
Methane!
Is there any place they can go to where they'll be safe?
You need to try it to get to the elevator, Seth. You
need to go now.
Come on!
The drills hit that methane.
We gotta stop the drilling.
Stop the drilling! Stop the drilling!
What does that mean, there?
Careful, guys. Careful.
I don't hear anything!
Targeting vehicle!
I got nothing!
Yes! Yes! We got one!
He's got someone. He's got time.
He's alive! He's okay!
We got dead men!
Where is he?
Where's Yaron?
Blunt let us go first.
He didn't make it into the shaft and uh...
With the fires.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
FBI is here. What do you want to do?
I'm gonna go get Yaron.
I'm gonna go get him.
FBI is here. What do you want to do?
You talk, I'll watch, okay?
Okay.
Kevin Warren?
Yeah?
You have a right to remain silent?
What?
Anything you say or do can be used against you.
Are you kidding me? What? What is this?
You found out there was nothing underneath this site.
And you knew it would derail this project.
That's crazy.
And you tried to bribe the city engineer to sign off without
proper inspections.
That's crazy. I would never do anything to risk my guys' lives.
And if there was methane, I didn't know about it.
That's the truth.
I know you didn't because you showed true surprise when you were
accused.
Everybody here was surprised, outraged.
Except for one.
One person was relieved.
When a guilty person sees someone accused of the crime that they
committed, they show relief.
Your father tried to bring a factory to Frostburg when he was
mayor and he couldn't.
Is that how you found out about the methane?
I never thought anything like this could happen.
I didn't. I didn't.
We needed the jobs.
I'm sorry.
It's getting dark and it's getting cold and the nights are getting
long.
Hands on your back, man.
And I don't know if you'll even notice it.
This way. Hands on your back.
And I'm long gone, baby, long gone.
And the things that keep us apart keep me alive.
The things that keep me alive keep me alone.
Hey.
I thought you could use a real drink.
Panabaph.
Well, I can't help you with that.
I'm sorry.
Why do people always think they're the only one with a secret?
Human nature, I suppose.
If the mayor had told the truth or Blunt had been honest
about his illness, none of this would have happened.
If the lies hadn't come together.
I always do.